Well, Alex congratulations
亚历克丝 恭喜你
through to the semifinal here.
闯进了这里的半决赛
The crazy Yes.
太好了
round of applause.
掌声送给她
Come on.
来吧
The crazy thing is the last semi-final you made
离谱的是 你上一次打进半决赛
was not that long ago in Berlin and you beat
也没过多久 就在柏林
your same opponent the same score line.
对手一样 比分也一模一样
What I know it's nuts.
我知道 这太离谱了
What is it about playing Elina
跟斯维托丽娜交手
that brings out the best in you
为什么总能让你打出最好的状态
as such a great player that you have to beat?
她可是你必须战胜的强手
I don't think that it's specifically
我不觉得有什么特别的原因
because of who I'm up against.
不在于对手是谁
I think uh I came in with a great mindset today.
我想是我今天上场时心态很好
I think I was playing really well
我觉得自己打得确实不错
and of course Elina hit some good shots.
当然斯维托丽娜也打出了好球
She was being aggressive,
她很有攻击性
especially in that second set.
尤其是第二盘
So, I'm really happy that I was able to kind
所以我很高兴自己
of keep my rhythm.
大体保持住了节奏
What you are learning along the way?
这一路你学到了什么
This is really your first full year on tour
今年才是你真正完整的巡回赛年
after last year, but what is it that you're learning
那你学到的是什么
about yourselves in these moments,
在这些时刻 关于你自己
in these types of matches, in this atmosphere?
在这样的比赛 这样的气氛下
Oh, there's so many things
我学到的东西太多了
that I've learned about the tour, about myself,
关于巡回赛 关于我自己
about kind of what it takes to sustain this level,
关于维持这个水平需要什么
both physically and mentally,
身体上和心理上都是
and just the effort you need to have to, you know,
还有你必须付出的努力
hang with these top players and stay there.
才能跟顶尖球员周旋并站得住
And it's definitely a long process.
这肯定是个漫长的过程
I'm not I'm just at the beginning
我不是 我才刚刚开始
of that learning process.
还在这个学习过程的起点
So, I'm really excited for what's ahead.
所以我对接下来非常期待
Now, I know your next opponent, Naomi Osaka,
你的下一个对手是大坂直美
which is going to be an amazing match
这一定会是一场精彩的对决
between the two of you.
就在你们两人之间
You're all very excited about it.
大家都很期待
What are your thoughts about playing Naomi?
跟大坂直美交手你怎么看
And I'm sure you've grown up also watching her.
我想你也是看着她长大的
Yes, she is of course such an accomplished player
是的 她当然是非常有成就的球员
and I think she's made waves on and off
我觉得她在球场内外
the tennis court uh for so many reasons
都掀起过波澜 原因有很多
and uh there's so much respect
我对她有太多敬意
for her for that and you know I'm really excited.
就为这个 而且我真的很期待
Um I haven't had much time to think about it
我还没什么时间去想这件事
but I will definitely think about it
但我肯定会好好想想
after I get off court.
等我下场之后
Yeah. Well, I'm going to give you one more chance
好 我再给你一个机会
to thank all your Filipino fans.
去谢谢你的菲律宾球迷
They're in the crowd here.
他们就在现场看台上
So, whatever you want to say, the mic is yours.
想说什么都可以 话筒交给你
Ladies and gentlemen, through the semifinals,
女士们先生们 她闯进了半决赛
Alexandra Eala
伊埃拉